Every Step Has Led To This
Step Up All In is a romance, drama, music film directed by Trish Sie.
All-stars from previous installments convene in glittering Las Vegas, battling
for a victory that could define their dreams and their careers.
Andie West, played by Briana Evigan.
Sean Asa, played by Ryan Guzman.
Sophie, played by Chaton Anderson.
Jason Hardlerson, played by Stephen 'tWitch' Boss.
Eddy, played by Misha Gabriel.
Alexxa Brava, played by Izabella Miko.
Step Up: All In is a 2014 American dance film directed by
Trish Sie and written by John Swetnam.
The film is the sequel to Step Up Revolution (2012) and the fifth
and final installment in the Step Up film series.
It stars Ryan Guzman, Briana Evigan, Stephen "tWitch" Boss, Misha
Gabriel, Izabella Miko, Alyson Stoner, and Adam Sevani.
Step Up: All In was released in the United States on
August 8, 2014, by Summit Entertainment.
The film grossed over $86 million worldwide and
received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of dance competition, street artist, woman director.
The tone is emotional.